What's the best anabolic TRT dose for
muscle growth?
So, as you know, as a doctor, it's a
it's a difficult one to just sort of
answer without being a without being
like crucified by your colleagues. So,
what I say is our job is to get your
levels safe and the rest is up to you.
Um so uh that doesn't mean so some some
people they'll see a health practitioner
and they get their level just one point
above the minimum and are told they're
fine and then their symptoms are
ignored. That's definitely not my
approach. I definitely aim for the upper
third of the normal limit. Uh keeping an
eye on things like your hematocrit and
stuff like that as well. So obviously
safety is a concern but we want it as
high as possible giving the maximum
symptom relief but all but also being
safe. That's
paramount in terms of muscle growth. The
rest of it down to your own lifestyle.
Are you eating right? Are you training
right? Are you doing all these things
sensibly? And then I don't see any
reason that if your testosterone is
normal, you can't gain a significant
amount of muscle mass. You can get
extremely big by just training right and
eating right. And and I think looking
for a high number for performance
enhancing and things like that. Um the
the safety issues far outweigh those
benefits long term.
[Music]